

NUNO ANTUNES

Cloud Engineer

- @ nantunes00@gmail.com
- in nuno-antunes-00
- dreadster3

- **J** +971 ...
- Dubai, UAE
- **J** +351 ...
- Lisboa, Portugal

STRENGTHS

Logical Thinking | Resilient

Quick Learner Self-Learner

Open Minded

Self-Motivated

Inquirer |

Problem Solver

ABOUT ME

I'm a dedicated programmer who finds joy in coding during my spare time. I'm particularly passionate about creating new open source projects, believing in the value of collaboration and community. Mostly recently, I have been delving into CTF challenges, which sparked my interest in computer security, through platforms like Hack The Box and TryHackMe. Currently, I work as a cloud engineer, specializing in GitOps, where I collaborate with a team to provide an Azure landing zone for clients. It's an exciting role that allows me to blend my programming skills with cloud technology to deliver efficient and reliable solutions.

SKILLS

C++ Java Python

PHP C# (Java/Type)Script

Python SQL NoSQL

Go Rust Terraform

LaTex

CI/CD Linux | Git |

WebAPIs | Virtualization

Containerization

Cloud Native Computing

EXPERIENCE

Cloud Engineer | Saint-Gobain | •

10/2022 - On going

Lisbon, PT

Involved in the development of an Azure landing zone. Mostly built around terraform modules.

Software Engineer | Vision-Box | •

= 08/2021 - 10/2022

Lisbon, PT

Lead developer regarding any project or solution necessary to the Emirates Project.

Project Collaboration | Netcompany | •

= 4/2021 - 07/2021

Remote

Developed a prototype mobile application to improve the studielink platform.

LANGUAGES

Portugese: Native

English: Proficient

Spanish: Beginner

System Administration | Micro-R |

12/2020 - 01/2022

Remote

Responsible for taking the monthly reports for Micro-r's clients.

Website Maintenance | Zonaplus | •

10/2020 - On Going

Remote

Responsible for rewrite and maintenance of the website.

REFERENCES

Inês Simão - Vision-Box

in nessimao

EDUCATION

BSc Computer Science & Engineering | Delft University of Technology

September 2018 - June 2023

Delft. NL

International Baccalaureate | GEMS Wellington Academy

September 2014 - June 2018

Dubai, UAE

PROJECTS

Azure Landing Zone | Saint-Gobain

i 10/2022 - OnGoing

Took part in the development of the azure landing zone used by saint gobain. This development made use of:

- Terraform
- Terratest
- Python
- Github + CI/CD
- Go

Emirates | Vision-Box

i 09/2021 - 10/2022

Took part in the development of the solution Emirates has implemented regarding all of their automated boarding gates. Solution made use of:

- Rabbit MQ
- ASP NET
- Elastic Search
- State Machines
- WSO2

Studielink Improvement Prototype | Netcompany

= 04/2021 - 07/2021

Project consisted of creating a prototype mobile app with possible improvements to studielink.

Technologies used:

- Frontend: React Native (Javascript)
- Backend: Spring Boot (Java)
- Version Control: Gitlab + CI/CD

Mars Rover Project | TU Delf

11/2020 - 02/2021

Developed a hardware simulation of a simplified Mars Rover, using VHDL.

Laser Reflection | TU Delf

i 02/2019 - 04/2020

Java game developed using different OOP design patterns.

Developed using a scrum approach.

Ray tracing | TU Delf

i 09/2019 - 11/2019

Developed in C++.

Raytraces any scene and generates a picture with the final result.

GoGreen | TU Delf

= 02/2019 - 04/2019

Developed a server-client application to track CO2 emmissions.

The Application was developed in java and using a scrum approach.

Technologies used:

- Frontend: Java Swing (Java)
- Backend: Spring Boot (Java)

Version Control: Gitlab + CI/CD

Battleship | TU Delf

11/2018 - 01/2019

Developed a web application that allows 2 users to play the battleship game online.

- Frontend: HTML + JS + CSS
- Backend: NodeJS (Javascript)

PROFESSIONAL TRAINING AND CERTIFICATIONS

Certifications:

AZ-900: Azure Fundamentals (Microsoft)

Training:

- Agile Foundations Training
- Relationship building for buddies Training
- Querying Data with Transact-SQL Training
- Kubernetes (Microsoft) Training
- ITIL Training

ACADEMIC ACHIEVEMENTS

- Awarded 3 times in a row as the best Computer Science student.
- Participated in KHDA Hackathon, workshop given by IBM.
- Math competitions for 7 years.
- Teaching assistant at GEMS Wellington Academy.

OPEN-SOURCE CONTRIBUTIONS

Buddy | G dreadster3/buddy

A language agnostic CLI to help automate your development workflow.

Media CLI tool for quick media transformations

Dashboard for github with focus on workflow management

Python Query | • dreadster3/python-query

Similar to react-query but for python

Utility to fix background and polybar when x11 is resized in VM